no1reviews.com 2010-04-05

# No1Reviews.com Privacy Policy

At No1Reviews.com, we take your privacy seriously. We will never sell or disseminate any personal information about you or your business. 

Our privacy policy is outlined in full below... 

Information Collected

No1Reviews.com will not collect any personal identifiable information from you unless you voluntarily submit such information, e.g. by signing up to our newsletter.

|   |   
  
---|---|---  
  
In common with many other websites, No1Reviews.com does collect non-personally identifiable information for use in generating statistical data in order to help us market our recommended products more effectively.

Our Newsletter

When signing up to our newsletter/ecourse we will collect your name, e-mail address and any other preferences or personal information that you voluntarily submit to us. This information is used to send you our newsletter/ecourse and from time to time we may use this information to send you details of any special offers we may be promoting that we think you may be interested in. 

Our newsletters operate a double opt-in policy, meaning that in order to receive e-mails from us, you must first enter your name and e-mail address on the subscription form on our website (usually located in the menu bar), and then you must confirm your subscription to our newsletter by clicking on a confirmation link that we send you. Only then will you be added to our mailing list. This prevents anyone else from maliciously adding your e-mail address to our mailing list. This double opt-in system is in compliance with current CAN SPAM laws and ensures that you will only receive mail from us if you yourself subscribe and confirm your subscription to our newsletter.

Opt-out Policy

Each and every e-mail you receive from us will have an opt-out link at the bottom, should you wish to unsubscribe from any of our newsletters. This is in compliance with current CAN SPAM laws. You can unsubscribe from our mailing lists at any time by clicking on this link. You will then be taken to another page which will ask you to confirm your wish to unsubscribe from our mailing list. If you choose to unsubscribe you will never receive any e-mails from us again. Should you choose to re-subscribe to any of our mailing lists then please subscribe again using the online form provided (usually located in the menu bar).

Use of Information

Any personally identifiable information you send us (e.g. by subscribing to our newsletter, or by mailing us) will only be used by us. We will never sell, rent or otherwise disseminate your personal details to any other website, business or individuals. If you choose to unsubscribe from our mailing lists then you will never again receive notifications from us of any kind. 

Use of Cookies

In common with many other websites, No1Reviews.com may use cookies to track your navigation around our site. These cookies are tiny text files that are placed on your hard drive and help us determine which keywords you used in the search engines that brought you to our site. Cookies, together with affiliate links, are also used to track your purchases from any of our recommended sites. The use of cookies (and the use of affiliate links) is completely harmless to you or your computer and is common practice on most websites.  

Third Party Sites

No1Reviews.com links to many other sites as part of our effort to provide a service to our users. No1Reviews.com cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies of the other sites that we link to, and so we encourage our visitors to read these privacy policies before purchasing from or using the services offered by these third party websites.

Policy Changes

No1Reviews.com reserves the right to make changes to our privacy policy without notice. Users are encouraged to review this document regularly to stay informed of any policy changes. 

Acceptance of Terms

By continuing to read and use this website, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy and of our Terms and Conditions. If you do not accept this Privacy Policy or do not accept our Terms and Conditions then please leave this site. 

How to Contact Us 

Please use the Contact Us link at the bottom of this page to contact us. 

[FAQ](http://www.no1reviews.com/faq.html) | Useful Links | Site Map | [Terms & Conditions](http://www.no1reviews.com/TC.html) | [Webmasters](http://www.no1reviews.com/webmasters.html) | [Contact Us](http://www.no1reviews.com/Contact.html)

Web site and all contents © Copyright No1Reviews.com 2020, All rights reserved.  
Reproduction in whole or in part in any form or medium without express written permission of No1Reviews.com is strictly prohibited. Plagiarism will be detected immediately by Copyscape. Copyright theft has been dealt with harshly in the past. Our policy is to immediately file DMCA complaints and federal copyright infringement lawsuits against any webmaster caught stealing content from No1Reviews.com and to press for statutory damages as high as $150,000 as set forth in Section 504(c)(2) under 17 U.S.C. Section 101 et seq.
